我有个跟蝙蝠人有关的问题
I have a question about Batman.
蝙蝠人是个穿得像蝙蝠的人
Batman is a man who dresses up like a bat.
人蝠是半人半蝙蝠的混种生物
Man-bat is a part man, part bat hybrid.
如果人蝠打扮成人去打击犯罪
Now, if Man-Bat dressed up as a man to fight crime,
那他会变成人蝙蝠人吗
would he be Man-Batman?
不会  他会变蝙蝠人蝠
No, he'd be Bat-Man-Bat.
但是人蝙蝠人不应该是蝙蝠人
But wouldn't Man-Batman just be a Batman
如蜘蛛人就是被放射性蜘蛛咬过后
才获得类似蜘蛛般的能力
被放射性人类咬过之后的样子吗
that was bitten by a radioactive man?
但蝙蝠人本来就是人啊
But Batman is a man.
你刚才说人被赋予人的能力
You're talking about a man who would have the powers of a man.
就像是人类吃了人人果实
That's just Man-Man.
但人人其实不就是人而已吗
Well, isn't Man-Man just man?
但要是人人穿成像蝙蝠呢
But what if Man-Man dressed as a bat?
那就是蝙蝠人啊
Well, that's just Batman.
不对  一个人穿上蝙蝠装
No, if a man dresses as a bat,
那是蝙蝠人  但如果是人人穿上蝙蝠装
that's Batman, but if Man-Man dresses as a bat,
那就是蝙蝠人人
that's Batman-Man.
这样算回答了你的问题吗
So does that answer your question?
我还没问我的问题呢
Oh, I haven't asked it yet.
是克莱尔  我得先走了
Oh, that's Claire. Got to run.
我还以为你跟艾米丽复合了呢
I thought you were back with Emily.
其实我...  同时在跟她们交往[看]
Uh, actually I'm... seeing both of them.
你是指躲在她们窗外草丛偷看的"看"吗
You mean like through their window from behind a bush?
不是  我是指同时跟两个女生交往
No, I'm actually dating two women.
回头见
Later.
不是吧
Really?
这多少年来不敢跟女人说话的人
The guy who for years couldn't even talk to women
居然突然就开始脚踏两条船
is suddenly going out with two of them?
-这怎么可能  -对啊
- How is that possible? - I know.
科学家一直试图用计算模型模拟这件事
Scientists have tried to reproduce it with computational models,
但所有尝试中  最后世界都会爆炸
but, in each case, the world blows up.
说真的  这家伙居然能享齐人之福
Seriously, that guy's dating two women?
翻译：穿着赛太公衣服被放射赛太公咬的赛
YY  猫中之王  别扭大菜
你为什么买了一个派对潜艇堡
What, why did you get a party sub?
大家要来玩  这样感觉有意思啊
People are coming over; it looked fun.
我们只是要一起看《权力的游戏》
Well, we're only watching Game of Thrones.
但派对潜艇堡意味着会有派对
A party sub implies it's a party.
但你会出席已意味着不会有派对
Your attendance implies it's not.
我喜欢派对的程度与一个普通人无异
I like a party as much as the next man,
前提是这普通人并不喜欢派对
as long as the next man doesn't like a party.
对了  你别忘了
Oh, by the way, don't forget,
明天是我们的室友协议季度大会
tomorrow is our quarterly Roommate Agreement meeting.
谢尔顿  我们不需要每三个月就开一次会吧
Oh, Sheldon, we don't need a meeting every three months.
你这个提议感觉就很值得
Well, it sounds like the kind of thing one would bring up
在明天的季度大会上提出呢
at a quarterly Roommate Agreement meeting.
你真走运  会议刚好在明天
Lucky for you it's tomorrow.
我告诉你  我是不会参加的
Oh, you know what? I'm not going.
你必须得参加
Well, you have to go.
明天是佩妮首次主持效忠宣誓呢
It's Penny's first time leading the Pledge of Allegiance.
这个会议根本就是浪费时间
This meeting is a waste of time.
比如决定要不要
Whether we make the switch
从早餐谷物产品A换到产品B这种事
from Post Raisin Bran to Kellogg's Raisin Bran
不需要经过议会程序来定好吗
should not require parliamentary procedure.
你知道其中一款里的葡萄干上有糖吧
You realize one of them has sugar on the raisins.
反正都是你一个人吃啊
You're the only one who eats them!
而你居然有幸能提出意见呢
And yet you get to weigh in.
民主  就是这么酷  对吧
Democracy-- it's pretty cool, isn't it?
我不参加  你也逼不了我
I'm not going; you can't make me.
那我们就走着瞧
Well, we'll just see about that.
怎么啦怎么啦
What is the problem?
他说明天不来参加室友协议季度大会
He says he's not coming to the Roommate Agreement meeting tomorrow.
那我不是白背了效忠宣誓词吗
Well, why the hell did I memorize the Pledge?
祝玩得愉快  我反正不参加
You have fun. I will not be attending.
行啊  你要是不想参加
Oh, fine. We don't have to have
我们以后可以不办室友协议季度大会啊
a Roommate Agreement meeting if you don't want to.
-谢谢  -但这件事需要经过投票表决
- Thank you. - Of course, it will require a vote.
遗憾的是  我的正式木槌放在房间里
Unfortunately, my official gavel is in my bedroom,
但好在我的旅游随身木槌在这
but luckily, I have my travel gavel.
你是在耍白痴
You're being ridiculous.
有一个动议"谢尔顿是在耍白痴"
There's a motion on the floor, "I'm ridiculous."
有人附议吗
Do we have a second?
无人附议
There is no second.
动议驳回
The motion is denied.
下次请确保有人会投票
Next time, make sure you have the votes first.
刚才也太丢人了
That was embarrassing.
你能跟他说说吗
Can you please talk to him?
你为什么要跟他争这事啊
Well, why are you fighting him on this?
因为我受够了什么事都得顺他意
Because I am tired of him always getting his way.
我们又不需要这傻逼大会
We don't need a stupid meeting.
我们甚至都不需要狗屁《室友协议》
We don't even need a Roommate Agreement,
而且我还真希望这潜艇堡能招来派对呢
and I hope that sandwich does cause a party!
我还是会来参加你的大会
Well, I will still come to your meeting.
希望如此啊  明天可是拍照日
Well, I should hope so. Tomorrow's picture day.
你为什么站他那边啊
Why are you taking his side?
因为这事对他很重要
Because it's important to him,
我们签署《室友协议》时  就同意了这事啊
and when we signed the Roommate Agreement, we made a deal.
你再这么讲话  很快就要荣升扛旗者了
Y-You keep talking like that, you're gonna make color guard.
-天啊  我真是心力交瘁  -对啊
- Man, I'm worn out. - I know.
想象一下如果真像游戏里那么跑动
Imagine if we were actually moving.
不是啦  我是说自从我开始
No, it's just, ever since I started dating
跟克莱尔和艾米丽同时交往  真是精疲力尽啊
Claire and Emily at the same time, it's exhausting.
你这就精疲力尽啦
You're exhausted?
等你试过孕妇书里每五页就折个角
Try folding every five pages in a pregnancy book
好让你老婆觉得你有读  你才知道累
so your wife thinks you read it.
但兄弟  你很幸运了
But, dude, you're so lucky.
每晚能在家与你相爱的女人共度
Getting to stay home at night with the woman you love.
我的确很幸运
I guess I am lucky.
没错  如果你同时和两个女人约会
You are, because dating two women,
我是说  我都不记得
I mean, I can't even remember
上一次我睡在自己家是何年何月了
the last time I slept in my own apartment.
我每天醒来就想  "这是克莱尔还是艾米丽家
I wake up and I'm like, "Am I at Claire's or am I at Emily's?
还是某个我想不起芳名的新妞家"
Is there a third girl I've forgotten about?"
就像是
Like...
"我在谁家香闺啊"
"Where am I?"
拉杰
Hey, Raj.
准妈咪  你还好吗
Hey, how's the mommy-to-be?
还好  有点小累
Good. A little tired.
我感同身受  我最近和好几个妹子约会来着
I feel you. I've been dating multiple women.
你确定不跟我们一起看《权力的游戏》吗
You sure you don't want to come watch Game of Thrones with us?
你们自己慢慢看
You guys have fun.
我去床上窝着看书就好
I'm just gonna snuggle up in bed with a book.
听起来好爽啊  一个人独占一张床
Oh, that sounds great-- a bed to yourself.
我都想不起那种感觉是什么样了
Can't even remember what that's like.
你熟悉最新的《权力的游戏》剧情吗
Are you up-to-date on Game of Thrones?
应该是吧
Mm, I think so.
龙呀  雪僵尸啊
Dragons, snow zombies,
还有凡是长得帅的家伙都死了
and all the hot guys are dead.
这我可不确定了
Oh, I don't know.
席恩·葛雷乔伊的长相
Theon Greyjoy looks pretty good
对于没了小弟弟的人来说  相当不错了
for a guy who had his genitals cut off.
哎哟喂  有人还在闹小情绪呢
Uh-oh, somebody's still pouting.
别管我
Leave me alone.
如果是因为掉了一根"小棒子"
If it's because you lost a stick,
我知道它在哪里
I know where it went.
一点也不好笑
Not funny.
明知道会和好
You know you're gonna make up with him.
就不能直接跳到握手言和的那刻吗
Can we just skip to that part?
对  因为我是这里唯一一个成熟的人
Oh, of course, because I'm the only adult around here.
真的吗  唯一成熟的人
Really? The only adult?
没错
Yeah, that's right.
今晚我要看的节目可是标识为M.A.的
Tonight I'll be watching a show rated M.A.,
意思是成年观众  你个小屁孩
and that stands for "Mature Audiences," buster.
"唯一成熟的人"可不会因为
All right, you would think "the only adult"
一些蠢事而破坏别人整晚的情绪
wouldn't let something silly ruin our entire night.
我还以为你会理解我不爽的原因呢
And I'd think you'd understand why I'm annoyed.
只要你来参加大会  不就没这些事了吗
All this could be avoided if you'd just come to the meeting.
人家不想参加
I don't want to.
只是一个大会而已
Oh, it's just a meeting.
-一个简单的大会  -不要再提大会两个字了
- One simple meeting. - Stop saying "meeting"!
* 大会  大会  三四五六七 *
* Meeting, meeting, bo-beeting *
* 你不想听  我却偏要提 *
* Banana-fana, fo-feeting *
* 大灰  打毁  答慧 *
* Fee-fi mo-meeting... *
我带来了我的招牌菠菜蘸酱
I brought my famous spinach dip.
艾米  等一下
Yo, Amy, just one second.
* 大会 *
* Meeting. *
我不知道自己想要个儿子还是女儿
I'm not sure if I'm hoping for a boy or a girl.
如果生的是儿子
I mean, if it's a boy,
我就得教他玩接投球
I'm gonna have to teach him to play catch.
那我就得上网去查怎么玩接投球
Which means I'm gonna have to Google "How to play catch."
如果生的是女儿
If it's a girl, I mean...
她们那么天真无邪
they're so innocent and...
而你知道男人都是什么鬼样子
you know how guys are.
真的  男人都不是好东西
Totally, guys are the worst.
看看我
I mean, look at me.
我让艾米丽给我做了意大利烘蛋
I let Emily make me a frittata
然后把吃剩的留在克莱尔的冰箱里
and I kept the leftovers in Claire's fridge that night.
我真是个渣男
I'm such a dog.
你又来了
There you go again.
抱歉  我是不是抱怨得太多了
I'm sorry, have I been complaining about it too much?
其实你现在是在假抱怨
Actually, what you're doing is pretending to complain,
真显摆
but really trying to brag.
你怎么能这么说
How could you say that?
"人家真希望可以安静喝完一杯茶
"Oh, I wish could enjoy a cup of tea
而没有裸女在我身上跳来跳去"
without a naked girl bouncing up and down on me."
我从未说过这话
I never said that.
"人家记不得掉在沙发里的胸罩到底是谁的
"Don't you hate it when you can't remember whose bra it is
真是好讨厌哦"
you found wedged in your couch?"
好吧  这话我说过
Okay, that I said.
但这是真实的问题啊
But that's a real problem!
你把一个妹子的胸罩给了另一妹子
You give a girl another woman's bra,
你那晚上就别想和那妹子滚床单了
and you will not be having sex with her that night.
也许还能和另一个妹子睡  但这妹子绝对没戏
Maybe the other girl, but not her.
他怎么了
What's going on with him?
他为了参不参加
Oh, he's all bent out of shape
室友协议大会而闹别扭呢
about having a Roommate Agreement meeting.
这年头完美出勤率貌似不够酷炫了
Apparently, perfect attendance isn't cool anymore.
别担心  他会想明白的
Don't worry, he'll come around.
我能理解他为什么不高兴
Well, I get why he's annoyed.
那是你不明白到底是怎么回事
Well, then you don't understand what's happening.
你看
See...
莱纳德拒绝出席
Leonard refused to participate
一个强制性的室友协议季度大会
in a mandatory quarterly Roommate Agreement meeting.
这就是以巴特·辛普森为榜样养育下一代的恶果
This is what a generation raised on Bart Simpson looks like.
你明明自己也爱看《辛普森一家》
You love The Simpsons.
人家喜欢的是丽莎·辛普森
I love Lisa Simpson.
我能理解他的感受
Well, I know how he feels.
我就不喜欢咱俩的恋爱协议大会
I never enjoyed our Relationship Agreement meetings.
等等
Wait.
你之前都是假装的吗
You were pretending?
抱歉
Sorry.
不可能
No!
我不相信  我能分清真假
I don't believe you. I could tell.
"哇  谢尔顿
"Oh, Sheldon,
我从未想过在常务委员会里
I never thought re-filing a matter
重审一个议题会如此让人目眩神迷"
in a standing subcommittee could be so fascinating."
你觉得这是真是假
Hmm, what do you think?
你分不清吗
You don't know?
我是不是说了什么惹你不高兴了
Hey, did I say something to upset you?
没有  我没事
No, I'm fine.
是吗  因为通常我们都肩并肩一起上楼
Really? Because usually we walk side by side,
而今天我爬了两层楼梯
and I just went up two flights of stairs
都是跟在后面盯着你的屁股
staring at your bottom.
消停会儿吧
Just drop it.
好吧  我知道是怎么回事了
Okay, I think I see what's happening here.
你嫉妒我
You're jealous of me.
拜托
Oh, please.
你有什么好让我嫉妒的
What could you possibly have that I would be jealous of?
不是我有什么
It's not what I have,
而是我跟多少人一起"分享"
it's how many people I'm having it with.
走吧  谢尔顿  我们去对面看
Come on, Sheldon, we'll watch Game of Thrones over here.
乐意之极
Gladly.
好啊  走吧  我高兴还来不及呢
Oh, good, go. You know, it'll be nice to
终于看剧的时候没人在旁边说
watch an episode without someone saying,
"我看过原著
"I read the books.
别太喜欢上这个角色"
Don't get too fond of this character."
不全是因为他们会死啊
It's not always because they die.
举个例子  某角色是因为跟
In one case, it's because they've become involved
太古之初就有的地下的森林之子扯上关系
with underground tree people from the dawn of time.
是的  但我不会说是谁
Yeah, but I won't say who it is.
是布兰
It's Bran!
发生什么事了
Wait, what is going on?
莱纳德是个混球  所以我们要在这边看剧
Leonard's being a jerk, so we're gonna watch over here,
你们俩想跟我们一起看吗
Do you guys want to watch with us?
只要不跟他一起看就行
As long as I don't have to watch with him.
好啊  我也不想跟你一起看
Fine, I don't want to watch with you either.
我去那边
I'll go over here.
凭什么你来选
Why do you get to pick?
好  那你去那边好啦
Okay, then you go there!
老子爱去哪儿就去哪儿
Don't tell me where to go!
霍华德  你快进来吧
Howard, just come in here.
来这边  拉杰
Yeah, come on, Raj.
慢着  艾米有做菠菜蘸酱吗
Wait, did Amy make her spinach dip?
做了
She did.
老子会帮你吃光光
And I'm gonna eat it all!
到底发生什么事了
So what the hell happened?
我对谢尔顿的胡闹失去了耐心
Oh, I just ran out of patience with Sheldon's nonsense.
深有同感  我也受够拉杰了
Tell me about it. I've had it with Raj, too.
其实男人像女人一样
You know, like women,
每个月也会有荷尔蒙变化周期
men have a monthly hormone cycle.
睾丸激素的下降会导致男人易怒
Dips in testosterone can cause irritability.
有意思
Interesting.
或许我的男性周期刚好
Maybe my male cycle synced up
跟拉杰的女性经期同步了
with Raj's actual period.
如果谢尔顿的睾丸激素下降  他要变成蝴蝶了
If Sheldon's testosterone dipped, he'd become a butterfly.
可能有人上门赔礼道歉了
Maybe someone's here to apologize.
莱纳德
Hey, Leonard.
斯图尔特
Stuart.
这不是换装派对吗
Is this not a dress-up party?
不是
No.
从一开始就不是换装派对吗
Was it ever a dress-up party?
不是
No.
霍华德  你是不是告诉我这是换装派对
Howard, didn't you tell me it was a dress-up party?
是的
Yeah.
据说如果不爽霍华德  就应该来这边
I was told this is where to go if I'm mad at Howard.
我帮您把斗篷挂起来吧
May I take your cloak?
谢谢
Thanks.
这玩意一直被卷进我自行车的链条里
This thing kept getting caught in the chain of my bike.
我来给你说明一下情况
Well, I'll catch you up.
佩妮不爽莱纳德  莱纳德不爽我和佩妮
Uh, Penny is angry at Leonard, Leonard's angry at me and Penny,
我不爽莱纳德和艾米
I'm angry at Leonard and Amy,
拉杰不爽霍华德
Raj is angry at Howard,
我不爽乔治·R·R·马丁
and I'm angry at George R.R. Martin
因为他不出新书  害我不能跟莱纳德剧透
'cause there are no new books for me to spoil for Leonard.
你和霍华德怎么了
So what happened with you and Howard?
他嫌我不停说跟克莱尔和艾米丽约会的事
Says I was talking too much about dating Claire and Emily,
我说他就是嫉妒我
and I accused him of being jealous.
我也嫉妒你
I'm jealous.
我最接近跟两个女人约会的一次
Closest I've come to dating two women
就是我跟一个女人约会的那次
was that time I dated one woman.
真不知道你怎么受得了他
I don't know how you put up with it.
他简直有病  居然开个会
He's impossible. I mean, holding a meeting
来决定我们该买哪个早餐麦片
to decide what breakfast cereal we should buy.
有脆浆果的那款脆脆船长麦片  行了
Yeah. Cap'n Crunch with Crunch Berries, move on.
总之  艾米  谢谢你挺我
Anyway, Amy, thank you for sticking up for me.
老实说  我完全不在乎这事
Oh, I honestly couldn't care less.
我没听错吧
Sorry?
我挺你是因为有时我不爽
Well, I just took your side 'cause sometimes I get annoyed
佩妮和谢尔顿的关系那么亲近
at how close Sheldon and Penny are.
他们吵个不停好吗
Well, they argue all the time.
没有很亲啦
They aren't that close.
是谁总在他不高兴时安慰他
Who's always comforting him when he's upset?
-佩妮  可... -是谁
- Penny, but... - Who's the only one
能让他生病时把药吃下去
who can make him take his medicine when he's sick?
我试过把药藏进他的花生酱里
I try to hide it in his peanut butter,
但他吐了出来
but he spits it out.
好吧
Okay.
那你知道佩妮让他在《室友协议》里加了条款
And did you know she has him add things to the Roommate Agreement
让她既能得到想要的  又不用跟你吵架吗
so she can get her way and not fight with you about it?
这个贱人
Son of a bitch.
你乐什么
Why is that funny?
不知道  我喜欢幸灾乐祸
I don't know. I like the pain of others.
那你对这个肯定喜闻乐见
Oh, then you'll enjoy this.
伯纳黛特对你和库萨帕里也是一样的
Bernadette does the same thing with you and Koothrappali.
她才没有
No, she doesn't.
她总是替他说话
She defends him all the time.
她才没有
She does not.
是谁告诉你  不要再对他开甘地玩笑的
Who told you to stop making all those Gandhi jokes about him?
是她
Well, she did.
还有人力资源部
And human resources.
你觉得是谁让库萨帕里去人力资源部投诉
Who do you think told Koothrappali to go to human resources?
这个贱人
Son of a bitch.
你说得对  的确挺乐的
You're right, it feels good.
好了  游戏时间马上到了
All right, it's almost game time.
懂没
Get it?
《权利的游戏》  "游戏"时间
Game of Thrones, game time?
这也能俩女友啊
Two women, huh?
可能是艾米脑子终于转过来了
Oh, perhaps it's Amy coming to her senses.
什么事
What's up?
其实你没必要利用谢尔顿
You know, you don't need to use Sheldon to get your way with me
在愚蠢的《室友协议》里搞定我
in a dumb Roommate Agreement.
谁告诉你的
Where'd you get that from?
艾米
From Amy.
艾米  你为什么告诉他
Ugh. Amy, why did you tell him that?
因为你总是替谢尔顿说话
Because you were defending Sheldon like you always do.
我没有总替谢尔顿说话
I don't always defend Sheldon.
你有  你知道你自己对他有
Oh, yes, you do. You know you have a weird
诡异的姐弟加埃利奥特与ET情感
brother-sister-Elliott-E.T. Relationship with him.
埃利奥特是电影《E.T.外星人》中
与E.T.感情深厚的男主角
那你对他的诡异情感呢
What about your weird relationship with him?
那不一样
That's different.
我就像是鬼片里不怕死的小女孩
I'm like the little girl in Poltergeist
而他就是电视里的那个妖魔鬼怪
and he's the creepy thing in the TV.
各位
Um, guys?
食物里是不是有坚果啊
Were there any nuts in that food?
应该没有  怎么了
I don't think so. Why? Well...
就是有不祥的感觉
just a feeling.
它就叫意大利三明治
It just said "Italian sub."
我没想到意大利香辣肠里会有开心果
I had no idea mortadella has pistachios in it.
有意思小知识
Interesting fact:
在意大利语中  意辣肠的前半段有死亡的意思
In Italian, the "Morta" In "Mortadella" means death.
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
我可没说"有趣"小知识  我又不是冷血怪物
I didn't say "fun" fact. I'm not a monster.
他不会有事的
He's gonna be okay.
现在就是有趣小知识了
Now it's a fun fact.
天啊  这种事情真能让人更理智看问题
Boy, stuff like this really puts things in perspective.
你为什么穿成这样子
Why are you dressed like that?
霍华德骗我这是个换装派对
Oh, uh, Howard thought it'd be funny
他觉得看我出糗很有意思
to tell me it was a costume party.
这太坏了吧
That wasn't nice.
不过他差点死了  我们扯平了
No, but he almost died, so we're cool.
仔细想一想  其实今晚就像
You know, if you think about it, tonight was kind of like
现实版的《权力的游戏》
a real-life Game of Thrones.
怎么会
How?
霍华德吃下开心果
Well, Howard eating that pistachio
就像乔佛里被毒死那幕
was like when King Joffrey got poisoned.
可那是谋杀  这是意外
Okay, well, that was murder, this was an accident.
好的
Okay.
可你利用谢尔顿去干那些肮脏勾当
But you using Sheldon to do your dirty work
正像瑟后利用御林铁卫执行她的命令一样
is like when Cersei used the King's Guard to do her bidding.
瑟后是靠卖肉操控男人
Cersei uses her body to manipulate men.
佩妮只是带我去了乐高店
Penny just takes me to The LEGO store.
好的  那这个呢
Okay. Oh, how about this?
斯图尔特穿得像个守夜人的兄弟
Stuart's dressed like a brother of the Night's Watch,
而他们没女人睡
and they don't have sex.
-说得好  -没有错
- There you go. - That's true.
没瑕疵
Fair enough.
-你没事吧  -没事
- You all right? - I'm fine.
就是觉得被人像抱婴儿一样抱下楼
Just a little embarrassed I had to be carried down the stairs
有点丢人
like a baby.
谢了
Thanks.
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
太吓人了
That was scary.
重点是
Well, the important thing is
我说过那个三明治会毁了一切的
I said that big sandwich would ruin everything,
被我言中了吧
and I was right.
琼恩·雪诺
Hey, Jon Snow!
你的马上怎么还有个篮子
How come your horse has a basket on it?
你的脑袋上怎么还有张脸
How come your head has your face on it?
《权力的游戏》里可不会戴自行车头盔
They don't wear bicycle helmets in Game of Thrones.
虽然你装扮有瑕疵
You're thematically inaccurate,
但我为你的安全意识点赞
but I applaud your commitment to safety.
你们就没别的正经事可干了吗
Don't you guys have anything better to do?
比看一个穿皮草斗篷的人
Better than watching a guy in a fur cloak
骑妇女车还重要的事吗  没有
ride a girl's bike? Nope.
够了
That's it,
你们刚刚失去了漫画店里的厕所特权
you just lost bathroom privileges at the comic book store.
有篮子的马  一群傻子
Horse has a basket on it. Stupid...
莱纳德
Leonard.
莱纳德  莱纳德
Leonard. Leonard.
干嘛
What?
我还一直没机会问你那个蝙蝠人的问题
I never got to ask my question about Batman.
什么问题
What is it?
如果蝙蝠人被一个放射性的人蝠咬了后
If Batman were bitten by a radioactive Man-Bat,
然后穿成人蝠的样子去打击犯罪
and then fought crime disguised as Man-Bat,
那他是人蝠人蝠人吗
would he be Man-Bat-Man-Bat-Man
还是人蝠人蝠蝙蝠人
or simply Man-Bat-Man-Bat-Batman?
他在人蝠装的底下还穿着蝙蝠人装吗
Is he still wearing the Batman suit under the Man-Bat suit?
容我思考一下再回来
I'll be back.